http://www.martinbalmer.co.uk/privacy

Commission Art
About Me
Martin Balmer
Explore Art
BirdsBritish WildlifeLandscapes & SceneryMagical & FantasyPetsPortraits & PeopleWorld Animals
Privacy Policy
Privacy Statement
When using the MartinBalmer.com web site  your privacy is both protected and respected to the maximum possible extent. MartinBalmer.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for MartinBalmer.com and any web site that forms part of MartinBalmer.com denoted by the MartinBalmer.com header.
Information Automatically Logged
Your IP address is used to gather broad demographic information, such as which pages are downloaded most, number of actual people using this web site,   popular search terms and popularity of our pages around the world.
When Contact Details Are Requested
Should you need to provide contact details to MartinBalmer.com please be assured that these will be solely used for the purpose for which you provided them. MartinBalmer.com DOES NOT sell or share such information.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. MartinBalmer.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.
Advertising and Cookies
Google Analytics and Google Analytics Advertising Features are implemented on this web site.
Google advertising on this web site can be controlled from the Google Ad Preferences control page.  You can reach this by selecting ‘Ad Choices’ on an advertisement or ‘Ads by Google’ below an advertisement.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this   site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   info@martinbalmer.co.uk
Watercolour Pencil Drawings
Commission A Portrait
Paintings
Collections
Characters
Creative Writing
eBay
Etsy
WordPress
theme.
Copyright © 2004 - 2020 Martin Balmer. This web site and all of the content and artwork are copyright. The Martin Balmer hand, robin on a pencil and pine marten artwork are trademarks of Martin Balmer.Terms and Conditions | Privacy Policy | Contact Us
